Contact

flavius_ciprian99@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pintican-flavius-b92566104 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PHP

MySQL

SQL

Languages

French (Professional Working)
English (Professional Working)
Spaniolă (Limited Working)

Certifications

NodeJs Couse

Object Oriented Programming in JavaScript

Pintican Flavius

Software Engineer la Splend

Cluj County, Romania

Summary

As a PHP software developer I took part in a lots of projects from big to start-ups where

I achieved the deadlines, wrote a good quality of code, partcipated at meetings and gave solutions to the taks,

took project from scratch and became them an interesting beta version on the marketplace.

On all of the projects I worked with inside projects frameworks, but also with commercial frameworks like: Symfony from version 2 to 5, Phalcon 3.3, Laravel 5.7, or Slim 2 and 3.

I wrote also unit and integration tests, doing deploys using amazon services for a part of them, using pipelines for code analizes

As a career goals I want to be a system architect in the near future, improve my Javascript skills(ReactJs or NodeJs) or deep learn of Python.

Regarding skills I can mention some of them:

Excellent communication skills, persuasion and motivation Team spirit

Ability to analyze and solve problems

Able to easily learn and understand new concepts/ technologies

Dedication and hard work towards improving professional and social skills

About my experience I present to you bellow.

Experience

Splend
Software Engineer
October 2019 - April 2020 (7 months)
Cluj County, Romania

As a php developer I implemented new features and fix bugs for a inhouse project in splend company, an automotive industry which provide resources and a community for on-demand drivers wanting to be their best from dedicated support to advanced training and rewards.

Technology used:

PHP 7.1, 7.2, laravel framework 5.7. Unit tests and integration tests with php unit.

Bitbucket, Jira, Mysql, kibana, Aws services: elastic beanstalk, sqs, ec2, s3 etc. Using CD/CI tools. Working with 3 party applications like: Zendesk, Zoho, Fleetio, Geotab, Uber

AROBS Transilvania Software
PHP Software Developer
May 2019 - September 2019 (5 months)
Cluj County, Romania

As a PHP developer I worked for a romanian client in accounting domain and one month for a project which managed events for different companies in USA written in laravel 5.6.

Technologies used: PHP 7.2, PHP 7.3, PHP Unit, MYSQL, BITBUCKET, CD/CI tools, Symfony 4, Laravel 5.6
Also on this period I learnt NodeJs, some things about ReactJs and TypeScript, JavaScript OOP concepts

P4B Group
PHP Software Developer
April 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Cluj County, Romania

As a PHP developer I worked for a german client: HMM Deutschland to build new features or maintenance the website.

I was also involved to rewrite parts of the project in microservices, creating packages for microservices.

Technologies used: PHP 5.3, PHP 7.2, PHP Unit, MYSQL, GIT/SVN, Redmine, CD/CI tools, Phalcon 3.3, Slim 2.6

Greppy Systems
PHP Software Developer
March 2017 - April 2018 (1 year 2 months)
Cluj County, Romania

As a PHP developer I worked for several start-up projects for romanian or foreign clients like: TIFF festival, Untold, Carwash, Ace of King Poker, Banjo, or Travtus.

On every project that I worked I build REST API using Symfony 3.1 to 3.3 for clients like Mobile or Angular apps.

I used different Symfony bundles to achieve the clients expectations: twilio, swiftmailer, twig for templeting, OAuth 2.0, push notification, redis, memcached, DynamoDB from AWS etc.

Technologies used: PHP 5.6 to PHP 7.1, Symfony 3, MYSQL, NOSQL(DYNAMO DB, Mongo DB), GIT, JIRA, BITBUCKET, AWS: S3, Dynamo Db.

Bellow I described few things regarding the projects that I was involved:

TIFF a platform website which managed films in Romania, placed in Cluj-Napoca (which are new, by rating, or sells).

Untold festival a platform website which managed the largest electronic music festival held in Romania, taking place in Cluj-Napoca.

Carwash a mobile app which managed washing cars in Romania, taking place in Cluj-Napoca.

Ace of King Poker a mobile app which managed all the activities on a poker table for Israel clients

Banjo a mobile app, a chating family like Whatsapp or Facebook Messanger. Travtus a website and mobile app which manged creating, estimations, buildings from scratch or managed activities of the tenants inside of the buildings.

Pentalog

1 year 4 months

PHP Software Developer February 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 1 month) Cluj County, Romania

As a PHP developer I implemented new functionality and fixing bugs on the project MEETIC, a big dating website across western Europe.

On the project I used technologies like: PHP 5.3, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQUERY, MYSQL, JIRA, GIT, but sometimes PHP 5.6, Symfony 2.7 and PHP Unit

Intern PHP Software Developer November 2015 - January 2016 (3 months) Cluj County, Romania

During the internship program I learnt the basic concepts of the following technologies: PHP, MYSQL, GIT, JIRA, HTML, CSS, JQuery and Javascript. Also I did a small project inside of a team formed by 4 members using Symfony 2.7 and writing unit tests with PHP Unit.

The project was built to manage the holidays, sick days or unpaid holidays for every employee from the company.

Freshbyte Intern PHP Software Developer July 2015 - July 2015 (1 month) Cluj County, Romania

During the internship program I learnt the basic concepts of the following technologies: PHP, MYSQL, BITBUCKET, JIRA, HTML, CSS and Javascript. Also I did a small intern project inside of a team formed by 3 members using the technologies mention earlier.

The project was built to manage the entire activity inside of the company: projects, developers, managers, etc.

Education

Faculty of Matematics and Computer Science Licentiate degree, Computer Programming (2013 - 2016)